zionsbank.com 2016-05-06

# FACTS

                                                                                                                    07RRD102715
                                                                                                               Rev. 01/2016
  FACTS              WHAT DO ZB, N.A., AND ITS AFFILIATES
                     DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
  Why?               Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some, but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                     how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                     understand what we do.
  What?              The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                     have with us. This information can include:
                         Social Security number and assets
                         income and account balances
                         transaction history and credit history
  How?               All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                     customers’ personal information; the reasons we choose to share; and whether you can limit this
                     sharing.
                                                                 Do ZB, N.A. and its
 Reasons we can share your personal information                                             Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                   affiliates share?
 For our everyday business purposes —
 such as to process your transactions, maintain
 your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                        Yes                           No
 investigations or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes —
 to offer our products and services to you                                 Yes                           No
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                        Yes                           No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
 information about your transactions and experiences                       Yes                           No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —
 information about your creditworthiness                                   Yes                           Yes
 For our affiliates to market to you                                       Yes                           Yes
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                        No                      We don’t share.
To limit              Call the phone number listed below for the ZB, N.A. division or affiliate for which you are
                      interested in limiting sharing.
our sharing
                        Amegy Bank                                National Bank of Arizona       Zions Bank
                           1-888-423-7063                            1- 866-299-3342                1-866-299-3338
                        California Bank & Trust                   Nevada State Bank              Zions Capital Advisors
                           1-866-299-3339                            1- 866-299-3341                1-888-557-7390
                        The Commerce Bank of Washington           Vectra Bank Colorado           Zions Direct
                           1-206-292-3900                            1-866-299-3340                 1-800-524-8875
                        The Commerce Bank of Oregon
                           1-503-548-1000
                      Please note:
                      If you are a new customer we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we
                      sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                      described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
                      Call the phone number listed above for the ZB, N.A. division or affiliate for which you have a
Questions?            question.

Page 2
Who we are
                                                      ZB, N.A., Amegy Investments, Inc., Amegy Mortgage Company, LLC,
Who is providing this notice?                         Amegy Insurance, Inc., Zions Direct, Inc., and Zions Capital Advisors, Inc.
What we do
How do ZB, N.A. and its affiliates protect            To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and
my personal information?                              use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These
                                                      measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                                       We also restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to
                                                       those employees who have a need to know such information.
How do ZB, N.A. and its affiliates                    We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?
                                                          open an account or provide account information
                                                          apply for a loan or make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                                          seek advice about your investments
                                                      We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                                      bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?                        Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                       sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information
                                                           about your creditworthiness
                                                       affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                       sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                      State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                      limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing
for an account I hold jointly with                    Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                            Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                      financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                           Our affiliates include Amegy Investments, Inc., Amegy Mortgage
                                                            Company, LLC, Amegy Insurance, Inc., Zions Capital Advisors, Inc.,
                                                            and Zions Direct, Inc.
Nonaffiliates                                         Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                      financial and nonﬁnancial companies.
                                                          We do not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                                       A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                                      together market financial products or services to you.
                                                          Our joint marketing partners include securities broker-dealers,
                                                           insurance agents and card issuers.
Other important information
ZB, N.A. provides banking products under the trade names Amegy Bank, California Bank & Trust, The Commerce Banks
of Washington and Oregon, National Bank of Arizona, Nevada State Bank, Vectra Bank and Zions Bank.
Depending on where you live, you may have additional privacy protections under some state laws. We will comply with
applicable state laws before sharing nonpublic personal information about you. We may do this by sending a separate
notice of those rights to you.
Nevada residents: We are providing you this notice pursuant to Nevada law. If you prefer not to receive marketing calls
from us, you may be placed on our Internal Do Not Call List by calling the number associated to the ZB, N.A. division or
affiliate noted on the first page of this notice, or writing us at Corporate Privacy, 550 North Hope Street, #300, Los
Angeles, CA 90071. For more information contact us at the address above, or email
NevadaTelemarketingOptOut@zionsbancorp.com. You may also contact the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of
the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington St., Ste. 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; telephone: 702-486-3132; email:
BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.
                                                                                                                         ZBNAPP 12/15
